Of course, because one is even afraid to
Конечно потому что один даже боится это
voice it, you are afraid,
озвучить вы боитесь
you are already like always Tai of my broadcasts
вы уже как за завсегда Тай моих эфиров
Yes, if I don’t come in, if I don’t come in, I get on you, you
Да как не зайду как не зайду на тебя
see, this is such magic Yes,
попадаю по видите это это магия такая Да
you are watching, we seem to be the third time Yes, we
вы смотрите мы мы вроде третий раз Да
are meeting Magicians Third yes Third yes here
встречаемся Маги Третий да Третий да вот
Yesterday or pose Yes, yesterday, it seems like just
вчера или поза Да вчера вроде как раз
three of these bombers at once took down
три этих бомбардировщика за раз уложили
ours Well, that’s enough from the American
наши ваших Ну хватит с американского
patriot, ours is nice It’s just nice Well,
патриота наш приятно Приятно просто Ну
listen, it’s unpleasant for me Honestly speaking, I’m
слушайте мне неприятно Честно говоря я
in favor of not shooting down anything from
за то чтобы не ничего не не сбивали друг
each other so and so with and so look when  if
у друга так так с и так смотрите когда
they shoot down all the Russian planes, then there won’t
собьют все российские самолёты то уже не
be anything they won’t shoot down and it will be for
будет чего не будут сбивать и будет За
peace. Well, listen. Well, this is also an illusion, if you
мир Ну слушайте Ну это тоже иллюзия если
look at it realistically, it’s impossible,
смотреть реально то этого невозможно
probably look. Wait again, these
наверное смотрите Подождите ещё раз эти
planes were shot down on the territory of Ukraine.
самолёты сбили на территории Украины Так
So, what’s wrong with you? Well, you
что что вас Ну что тут плохого ну вы
know  I’m not sure of the reliability of this
знаете я не уверен в достоверности этой
information, but how many planes have already been
информации но Сколько самолётов уже по
shot down? It’s not yours; they’ve already
сбивали так не ваши ваши уже ваши ж
admitted it; I just haven’t read it; I have
признали признали Да я просто не читал
n’t seen it. I can’t comment.
не видел этого не могу прокомментировать
Well, which ones and where were they shot down? Which
Ну а какие и где сбили Какие на
Su-34 bombers are in the Kherson region? Those that I’m planning there
су-34 бомбардировщики те которые там
they threw bombs Wow, I don’t know it hasn’t
закидывали Ничего себе не знаю пока не
happened yet. I think we have
было Мне кажется у нас этой информации
n’t
не
received this information. Well, it’s amazing, it’s amazing
проходила Ну удивительно удивительно
in general Su 34 Well, I don’t know, but what they shot down with the
вообще Су 34 Ну я не знаю а чем сбили с
patriot trio
трио патриотом
is
получается
the same thing. Well, I don’t know because there are still
тоже Ну я не знаю потому что что ещё
trios left, you have a lot of them there  I have
остались трио у вас там много их
n’t yet understood the resolution of the question, they remained
ещё не понял постанов вопро остались
quietly blown Yeah And how many of them were
тихонечку подули Ага А сколько их
quietly blown Well,
потихонечку
I remember the information was
подули Ну я помню проходила информация в
mostly patriotic they are around Kiev you
основном пэтриот они вокруг Киева у вас
don’t have How many how many according to your data how many
нет Сколько сколько по вашим данным
patriots were destroyed in
сколько уничтожили патриота в
Ukraine last time I heard information
Украине последний раз слышал информацию
that the last delivery you have not yet received
что последняя поставка вы ещё не успели
them  deploy as soon as they arrived and
их развернуть только они приехали и
immediately it was covered Holy [ __ ] So how many
сразу там накрыло [__] Так сколько
of them have you already destroyed I know Well,
их сколько вы уже по уничтожали знаю Ну
as far as I heard somewhere,
насколько я слышал где-то
there is information I
ходи информация не знаю
don’t know the complexes she definitely has.  I just know
я не знаю я не знаю просто
these destroyed pat, but Russia, I don’t
я эти уничтоженные пат но Россия я не
know, there is a video
знаю есть-то видео
unif, but you understand correctly, this is the
униф но вы поймите правильно это то
weapon that is being hunted by
оружие на которое охотится охо
hunting, we must understand that they are a threat to these
охоти мы долж понимать им угроза этому
weapons, the number one threat, yes, an
вооружению угроза номер один да
attempt. I correctly understood that this is as soon as they
попытка Я правильно понял что это как
transport Ukraine e  almost at the
только возят Украину е чуть ли не на
border they cover right there with daggers it
границе накрывают сразу там кинжала это
was the last, the last some
была последня последняя какая-то
information that they were transporting there
информация что везли там
somewhere they tried, well, this is a large
где-то пытались ну это же большой
complex of the right things, it is necessary to deploy it, store it,
комплекс правильного надо развернуть это
deploy it Well, and so on, it seems that even before it
складировать развернуть Ну и так далее
had time to unfold, it seems
вот вроде бы ещё не успев развернуться
like it was destroyed  it
вроде как был уничтожен это такая
turns out like this, and this one that was shot down like
получается так а этот которым сбили типа
these three planes, is it some kind of new one or is
этих три самолёта это какой-то новый или
it one that they managed
это который успели
to deploy, I don’t know, it’s just amazing
развернуть не знаю просто удивительно
if they actually shot down three planes
если сбили реально три самолёта
itself Well, this is serious If it’s true, then
само Ну это серьёзно Если это правда то
it’s true, yes, we celebrated everything there yesterday  they were already
это это правда да это мы там вчера
chewing Well, I don’t know, I don’t know Well, look
жевали Ну не знаю не знаю Ну ну смотри
really, you see the score, you see five Patriots
реально счёт видите вы пять Патриотов
And we destroyed three planes in a day Like, of course,
уничтожили А мы три самолёта за день
you’re cooler than the type, yes, but
Типа вы конечно круче типа да но вот
let it
пусть
be nih Yes, no, so you’re actually five PTAs And
нь зань Да нет так вы вообще пять ПТА А
we, we At least three planes, but for  one day
мы мы Хоть три самолёта но за один день
we at least rejoice in understanding, but we have
мы хоть радуемся понима но у нас есть
this Elusive PTT, you
вот этот Неуловимый птт вы пять
destroyed five But this sixth [ __ ] drives
уничтожили А вот этот шестой [__] ездит
shorter and you won’t catch him Yes, he will
короче и вы его не поймаете Да он будет
shoot yours, it’s this sixth one Yes,
стрелять ваше именно вот этот шестой Да
he’s something completely new, he’s turned him around like that
какой-то уж совсем новый он он такой его
Yes, he's big, they've turned him around, but he's
развернули да он большой развернули но
constantly moving, driving
он перемещается постоянно ездит ездящий
Pet, you know how the Flying Dutchman was a
Пет вот знаете как Летучий голландец был
ghost ship
корабль призрак
Yes, a traveling
Да ездящий
Patriot, in need of a T Listen, when the
Патриот нуждающийся на Т Слушай когда
mirto comes, say peace, here's the world, they'll
мирто будет скажи мир вот мир будет ко
kill all the Russian planes, they'll give
убивают все российские самолёты дадут
us more God, it's a very long wait And look,
нам ещё Боже это очень долго ждать А
wait  I also read in the
смотрите подождите я ещ я ещё читал в
Russian news that in my
российских новостях что вот В моей
region, yes, in the city of Starokonstantinov, an
области да В городе староконстантинова
American F16 has already been destroyed at the airfield. By the way, they
на аэродроме уже уничтожили американский
also didn’t
тоже которые прямо в ангарах их тоже не
have time to get them right in the hangars. In short, I read that they were destroyed in trucks, they
успели Я короче читал угарал их в фурах
were brought disassembled there in the hangars,
привезли разобранные там в ангарах
and assembled  They
собрали и их Накрыли
also covered them as patriots, it turns out,
тоже их как патриоты получается
yes. It seems to me that this is just
да Мне кажется это вот как раз
information about patriots and not about and
информация про патриоты были а не про а
not about F16, no, not yesterday. Yesterday I read
не про F16 не не вот вчера Вчера я читал
about F1, but in
про F1 же угорал
short, well, I don’t know. And what are they for? Well, I don’t
короче ну не знаю А для чего их Ну я не
know yet  the issue regarding the F16 has not been resolved Yes,
знаю пока же не решён вопрос по F16 Да
it has not been resolved, but yours have already destroyed
он не решён но ваши уже уничтожили
somewhat in short the entire supply of which Well, there
несколько короче всю поставку которую Ну
is no such information No, frankly,
нет такой информации Не ну откровенно
I read the news so sometimes I see, I understand And
читаю новости так иногда смотрю понял А
look, when they deliver the F16 to us, you will
смотрите когда когда нам F16 поставят вы
also cover them all at once, yes Or while
их тоже сразу всех накроет да Или пока
Petri This is from  you'll catch the sixth one,
Петри Это от того будете ловить шестого
listen Well, I looked at the opinion of
слушайте Ну смотрел мнение специалистов
military experts on the F16 Yes, I read that
по военных экспертов по F16 Да читал что
it's crap Well, it's not that much of a
это [__] Ну это не такой уж не такой уж
modern plane, honestly, that is, it's
современный самолёт честно то есть это
crap, in short, well, let's not say that it's
[__] короче да ну не скажем что это
absolutely crap But nevertheless, it's not the same
совсем там [__] Но тем не менее не та
the problem is how it is inflating Russia doesn’t care at all
проблема как э раздувается России вообще
F16
пофиг F16
Well, to be honest, let’s
Да ну честно говоря
say there’s a hundred some kind of anxiety
особой скажем так ста какая-то тревоги
about F116 No, well, of course there’s
по поводу f116 Нет ну конечно
trouble But only an increase in
неприятности А только увеличение
costs Yes, of course, they will have to be
расходов Да понятно их надо будет чем-то
destroyed with something. So it will be necessary.
уничтожить Значит надо будет А зачем
Why destroy them if they  In short, they’re
зачем их уничтожать если они короче там
ineffective, they don’t reach anywhere,
неэффективны никуда не достают угрозу
they
Они
pose a threat. They pose a threat. Well, any flying object. The
несут какую Ну любой летающий объект
drone now poses a threat. So wait, then. So, stop, I don’t understand, then
Дрон сейчас несёт угрозу Так подождите
F16, in short,
то Так стоп то не понял то F16 короче
they’re bad, not bad, I almost can’t
что они плохие неплохие я чуть не могу
understand, they’re not a threat, they’re not [ __ ], no
понять то не угроза то не [__] нет По
Compared to the new modifications  Yes,
сравнению с новыми модификациями Да
of course, it’s a little outdated, especially more likely, most likely,
конечно это немножко устаревший тем
as usual,
более наверное скорее всего как обычно
Western countries will deliver not the most
страны запада поставят не самые
modern version of the F16, you know, some old
современные вариант F16 понимаете старый
scrap metal, yes, without
металлолом ки какой-то да да без
phased
фазированных
radars and so on, but it’s not quite
там радаров и так далее но он не совсем
old, but still they will be
старый но всё-таки они будут устаревшими
a little outdated like that  that is, it’s not that right away, well,
немножко так то есть это не чтобы сразу
without illusions, it’s not f35 and not well,
ну без иллюзий это не f35 и не ну ясно
look clearly in the same way as, for
смотрите так же как например
example, C3 and C2 Yes, in chess these are
например C3 и C2 Да в шахматах это
different squares and C4 is a different square Yes, this is
разные клетки и C4 разная клетка Да это
completely and e6 and E5 are also different and it’s clear that
совсем а е6 и Е5 тоже разные и ясно что
f35 and F16
f35 и F16
once Well, why am I just saying this
раз Ну я к чему просто это говорю
since you understand this is not a threat that is
раз понимаете это не та угроза с которой
impossible to fight, to put it mildly,
невозможно бороться если мягко говорить
not Well, I agree if you are sree If you are five
не Ну согласен если сри Если вы пять
systems
систем
Of course, I hoped that now they would
Конечно я надеялся что вот сейчас F16
give F16 even more fun, something
ещё дадут ещё веселее будет что-то там
will click there your more
будут щёлкать ваши ещё
airplanes don’t No, why make me happy,
самолётики не Не ну что веселеть меня
it does
это как бы не радует вот откровенно ну
n’t make me happy, but frankly, it doesn’t make you happy Yes, I
вас не радует Да я
agree. Just think about where they
согласен Вот вы вы подумайте где они
will be based.
будут базироваться
A16 needs to be serviced Where will they be
а16 нужно обслуживать Где будут
serviced at
обслуживать на
airfields? Well, the airfield is immediately
аэродромах Ну аэродром сразу это же
visible, I’ve never seen a
видно
flight there.  now it’s
сни лет что туда полет так и сейчас
flying everything is flying there Well listen No well
летит всё летит туда Ну слушайте Нет ну
now it’s flying there less as if heavy
туда сейчас летит менее как бы тяжёлые
everything is
ве всё
flying every alarm everyone is already like this and all
летит каждая тревога уже все такие а всё
this in short the bastards are attacking Tarkon this is the
это короче падлы атакуют таркон это
Kirovograd
Кировоградская
region the threat is different If we suddenly reach
область угроза другая Если вдруг дойдём
such madness and that these planes
до такого безумия и что эти самолёты
will be based on let’s say  the
будут базироваться допустим на
territory of
территории
Poland and Romania to carry out combat missions from
Польши Румынии выполнять боевые задачи с
their territory then this, of course, is an
ихней территории тогда это конечно
increase in rates, a completely different conflict,
повышение ставок совсем другой конфликт
so that increase you just
что так что повышение вы просто калибром
hit Poland or Romania with a caliber And what will they
ударили в Польшу или в Румынию И что вам
tell you? Well, listen, these are serious things,
скажут Ну слушайте это серьёзные вещи
of course, well, hit the airfield in Rzeszow,
конечно ну ударите по аэродрому в жешуве
for example, and what what  Someone will tell you something
например и что что Вам что-то кто-то
why this is an increase in rates,
скажет к че это повышение ставок
expansion You are an
расширение Вы же взрослый
adult, you understand the sun,
человек ВС понимаете поприкалываться
you can laugh, but in fact this is a
можно посмеяться Но на самом деле это
round of tension, very
виток виток напряжённости очень
serious, funny And what is the current level of
серьёз прикольно А Какой сейчас уровень
tension in my opinion,
напряжённости на мой взгляд
yes, well, you know Well, such a
да ну вы знаете Ну такой
VM
ВМ
Uno  w let's say yes there, well, somewhere
Уно ш допустим да там ну где-то там
around there by what gradation orange above
около по какой градации оранже выше
average if simpler above average above
среднего если проще выше среднего выше
average not the highest understood
средне не наивысшие понял
yes yes good but the question is I understand you
да да хорошо а вот вопрос я так Поня вы
said that you are for peace yes Well
же говорили что вы За мир да Ну да
look, I understand how I should
смотрите вот я понимаю как должен
peace will come Yes, Russian troops must
настать мир Да российские войска должны
leave the territory of Ukraine definitely and
покинуть территорию Украины однозначно и
peace will come And how do you see the world, well,
всё настаёт мир А как вы видите мир а ну
yes, I think that we need to sit down at the
да я думаю что надо садиться за стол
negotiating table, choose for you at the service station what
переговоров выбрать вам вам на СТО о чём
we must agree on. So I say we
мы должны договориться Вот я говорю мы
must sit down at the negotiating table and
должны сесть за стол переговорами
agree  Russia is [ __ ] leaving the
договориться Россия нахрен уходит с
territory of Ukraine and we will continue to
территории Украины и дальше будем
discuss reparations yes And
обговаривать репарации да А ваше
what is your proposal No no I think we need to
предложение какое Нет нет я думаю надо
look more realistically at Let's Here is
смотреть более реально на Давайте Вот
your proposal How do you
ваше предложение какое Как вы
see how do you see the world
видите как вы видите мир
wait I understand so we see the world
подождите понимаю так что мы видим мир
differently Yes the world is absolutely  in different ways
по-разному Да мир абсолютно по-разному
You are a very intelligent person, as
Вы очень понятливый человек то как как
you see, I said, as we see, there is a
вы видите я сказал как мы видим есть
task for Russia, the minimum task Yes,
зада вот для для России задача минимум
this is to
Да это
stop on the demarcation line,
м остановиться на линии разграничения да
yes, that is, to seize territories, wait
то есть захватить территории подождите
Yes Listen to the end and achieve, first of all,
Да Слушайте до конца и добиться в первую
the neutral status of Ukraine
очередь нейтрального статуса Украины
then maybe there will be some additional
потом может быть ещё дополнительная
federalization of Ukraine,
какая-то федерализация Украины
let’s say, let’s say you don’t
принципу допустим вам не кажется что
think that Ukraine still doesn’t seem to you that Ukraine
Украина ещ по вам не кажется что Украина
should pay additional reparations to
дополнительно ещё репарации должна
Russia
России
No, I think no, not PPP I thought
выплатить Нет я думаю нет не ППП Я думал
you wanted more [ __ ] like And you
вы больше хотите [__] типа А вы так
just stop here federalization
просто останавливаемся тут федерализация
Ukraine Don’t let us make
Украины Не давайте давайте ещё чтобы
reparations to Ukraine yet
Украина репарации пр
No, it’s a joke, but nevertheless, of
поте Не ну это так шутка но тем не менее
course, there should be a program for
конечно должна быть программа
restoring the Ukrainian economy first and foremost,
восстановления в первую очередь
no one wants to, no, there
Украины никто не желает нет так
already is a program for restoring the Ukrainian economy; it’s reparations from the
Украины уже есть это репарация с
Russian Federation. Yes, everything is clear here.
Российской Федерации Да тут всё понятно
Well  I understand how you look like that I don’t
Ну я понимаю как бы так смотрите Я не
understand why why again why do you need
понимаю а зачем зачем ещё раз зачем вам
Kherson Zaporozhye Crimea Donetsk Lugansk do you
Херсон Запорожье Крым Донецк Луганск вы
want peace or do you want
хотите мир или хотите эти территории
to seize these territories from Ukraine I can’t
захватить у Украины я не могу
decide, you know at the beginning of the
определитесь знаете в начале вот
special operation there was no such task you
спецоперации же не было такой задачи вы
need it  you need
вот вам вам нуже вам нужен
Kherson Yes, you know how you want it
Херсон Да вы знаете как вам это
specifically for you yes or no Do you need
конкретно вам да или нет Нужен вам
Kherson or no for me Well listen he’s like
Херсон или нет мне Ну слушайте он как бы
I’m a Soviet man look you want peace
я человек Советский смотри вы хотите мир
or the Zaporizhia
или запорожскую
region Yes no we want peace you here You
область Да нет мы хотим мира ты вот Ты
specifically want peace or the Zaporizhia
конкретно ты хочешь мир или запорожскую
region  listen, this is not a
область слушайте так не ставится
question
вопрос
about you, tell me either you want peace, you are a
по ты ты скажи либо ты хочешь мир Ты
peacemaker, yes, or you want the Zaporozhye
Миротворец да Либо ты хочешь запорожскую
region and
область и
peace, that’s why I started, that’s why I
мир Я же поэтому и начал поэтому я и
started with this question, what is for
начал с этого вопроса Что для есть для
you and for us, the minimum tasks, the
вас и для нас задачи минимума задачи
maximum tasks for you, for me  it seems the task is
максимума для вас Мне кажется задача
maximum - This is to preserve the maximum
максимум - Это сохранить максимальное
number of territories, to achieve a
количество территорий э добиться бы
speedy peace, to obtain
скорейшего мира получить гарантии
security guarantees, how can this be
безопасности каким путём это можно
achieved? Well, naturally, this is
добиться Ну естественно это
neutral, no, not again, you are running away,
нейтрали нене не ещё раз ты убегаешь
specifically, do you need peace or do you
тебе конкретно тебе нужен мир или тебе
need the Zaporozhye
нужна Запорожская
region of the EU, you know, probably not such
область ЕС вы знаете наверное не такие
moments exist  that in exchange for peace for
моменты существуют что в обмен на мир на
peace and for the fulfillment of other obligations
мир и на выполнение других обязательств
once again Why do you need the Zaporizhzhya region for
ещё раз Зачем тебе Запорожская область
you, you are sitting with your ass in Moscow
тебе ты сидишь своей задницей в Москве
Why are those Zaporizhzhya region, this is not decided by
Зачем те запорожска область это решаю не
me
я
Listen, I’m not in all regions and regions of
Слушай я не во всех областях и регионах
Russia
России
would you be ready to give up the Zaporizhzhya region
бы ты готов отдать запорожскую область
so that there is
чтобы был
world listen to the Zaporizhzhya region in exchange
мир слушайте запорожскую область в обмен
for
на
peace, what have you got Look, I’ll explain,
мир вы что гото Смотри да объясняю
look, it’s very simple You give the
смотрите т очень просто Вы отдаёте
occupied part of the Donetsk Lugansk
оккупированную часть Донецкой Луганской
Zaporizhzhya region to Kherson and Crimea Yes,
Запорожской области Херсонской и Крыма
Crimea too, yes Well, of course, yes, in return,
Да Крым тоже да Ну конечно да взамен ещё
look again, in return, look, Wait, don’t
раз смотри взамен смотри Подожди не
interrupt, look, in return, Yes, in return, we
перебивай смотри взамен Да взамен мы вам
We give you the freedom to withdraw the rest of your troops.
даём свободно вывести свои остаток войск
Yes, they didn’t bomb them and continue at the
Да не разбомбили их так и дальше на
world level, waiting for reparations and then there will be
миром уровне жда репарации и вот будет
peace. You probably know such ideas. How do
мир вы знаете наверное такие идеи Как у
you have them, they have the right to
вас они имеют право на быть на
exist? Yes, but it seems to me that they are
существование Да но мне кажется они
distant from the existing reality. I want
отдалены от реальности существующей Я
you now  I’m not asking about reality.
тебя сейчас не спрашиваю про реальность
I’m asking
Я спрашиваю
you whether you need the Zaporozhye region or
тебе Запорожская область нужна тебе или
not. Do you need the Zaporozhye
нет нужна тебе Запорожская
region if it is now Russian territory? Do you
область если она сейчас территория
need it? It means the Russian
нужна она нужна значит Российской
Federation, wait, maybe it’s Well, the composition of the
Федерации подожди может она Ну состав
Russian Federation, maybe it’ll be turned off
Российской Феде а может быть и выключено
later, yes And if the people tell Putin,
потом да А если народ скажет Путину
for example  Putin Why did we capture him?
например Путин А зачем мы захватили его
Let’s turn him back from Russia. The people
Давай выключим назад из Росси народ
will say if the people say so. Well,
скажет если народ так скажет Ну вот вот
you are part of the people. Let me now,
вы вы часть народа Давайте вот я сейчас
I ask all of the people of the Russian Federation from you
я всех из народа Российской Федерации от
first, are you ready to
прошу вы первый да готовы ли вы да
give Ukraine the
отдать Украине за
Kherson region for the region?  Donetsk
область э херсонскую область донецкую
region Lugansk region and
область луганскую область и
Crimea You know, I will immediately answer this
Крым Вы знаете я сразу отвечу на этот
question that this is unrealistic I’m not saying
вопрос что это нереально Я не говорю
realistically look 140 ml I ask you
реально смотрите 140 мл Я прошу вы
first first as a citizen of Russia I’m not
первый первый как гражданин России не
ready Why I’m not ready Why I’m not ready to
готов Почему не готов Почему не готов
give for Crimea at all why not Zami
дать за Крым вообще почему нето Зами
for you want war  continuation of the war
за хочешь войну продолжение войны
killing of Russian people the world so
убийство русских людей мир так мир
look at the world you give it away very simply you are the first
смотри отдаёте очень просто ты первый
to agree to give up the Zaporozhye
вот соглашаешься отдать запорожскую
region Kherson Donetsk Lugansk and
область херсонскую донецкую луганскую и
Crimea Yes, I still find 139 of these uh
Крым Да я ещё нахожу 139 таких ээ
millions or there is half the number of
миллионов да или там половину сколько
voters there Yes they say Yes Putin
там Избирателей Да они говорят Да Путин
signs the petition give Crimea to these Ukrainians
подписывает петицию отдай этим украинцам
And that’s all And we don’t want to fight, we want to
Крым И всё И мы не хотим воевать хотим
live like yes in peace. You will be
жить типа да спокойно Вот вы будете
the first in Russia who will say this, I
первым первым в России который скажет
want, I know, I’ll
так я хочу я знаете я вас
disappoint you once I disappoint you. You won’t find the
раз я вас разочарую вы Не найдёте 139
other 139 million. Yes, of course, because
остальных миллионов Да конечно потому
one is even afraid to voice it. You’re
что один даже боится это озвучить вы
afraid. Afraid.  because yes, you
боитесь Боитесь потому что вот да у вас
really have this cringe, yes you need this
прямо сжалось такое да вам нуж это
Zaporozhye region, we need the Kherson
Запорожская область нам нужна Херсонская
region Yes, let our Russian soldiers die
область Да пусть дохнут наши солдаты
there, whatever you
российские там
want, I will frankly say that
ска хотите я откровенно скажу что
let
давайте
us need an independent prosperous
нам нужна независимая процветающая
neutral Fraternal Ukraine, that’s what we
нейтральная Братская Украина вот что нам
need And within what borders will it be  This is the
нужно А в каких границах она будет это
next question, you know, if it
Следующий вопрос понимаете если она
becomes such, it will become such. It is
станет таковой станет таковой Именно
then that it seems to me that the issue with the borders
тогда мне кажется с границами вопрос
will be
будет
resolved. I understand, that is, I understand correctly. That is,
урегулирован понял понял то есть я
you are
правильно понимаю То есть вы
ready to take away a bunch of territories from Ukraine
готовы забрать у Украины кучу территорий
so that it can be independent.
для того чтобы она была независимой
So listen, no. We are ready, your
Так слушайте Не Мы готовы готов ваш
people are ready to vote.
народ голосовать
ref I'll tell you everything You're just me
реф я ва се скажу ты Ты просто я тебе с
You're a funny coward Just a funny coward
Ты смешной трус просто смешной трус
Look nene not everything come on now listen
Смотри нене не всё давай теперь послушай
to me You're a funny coward Yes a funny coward You're
меня ты смешной трус да смешной трус ты
afraid to even say that you're afraid to
боишься даже сказать что ты боишься
voice that you don't need the Zaporozhye
озвучить что тебе не нужна Запорожская
region Because you are what  the
область Потому что ты сы что к тебе
investigative committee will come to you there Why
придёт там следственный комитет Почему
How many times have we discussed
Сколь раз общались
sensitive
острые
topics, I openly express my thoughts to you
темы я тебе откровенно высказываю свои
Yes, but those things that concern
мысли Да но которые вот такие касаются
everything are written down in the Constitution, I won’t
всё в Конституцию записано я ничего не
say anything, no, we, and
скажу да нет мы а Харьковская область
you need the Kharkov region well, and
тебе нужна хорошо а Харьковская область
you need the Kharkov region, Kharkov, let’s say the
нужна тебе Харьковская допустим
Kharkov residents decide  So wait
харьковчане реша Так подожди
pppppp about the Zaporozhye wait about the
пппппп про запорожскую подожди про
Zaporozhye you’re talking like We’ve written it all
запорожскую ты говоришь типа Всё мы её
into the Constitution And about the Kharkov one Well, there
вписали в Конституцию А про харьковскую
was a referendum there, wait a hundred what kind of
Ну там референдум прошёл подожди сто
referendum first of all You have a
какой референдум во-первых Вы у вас
part, look you occupied only
часть смотри вы оккупировали только
part of the Zaporozhye region even without
часть Запорожской области даже без
Zaporozhye itself Yes And you say which one  -the
самого Запорожья Да И говорите какой-то
referendum
референдум
was held You know, to remove these questions
прошёл Ты знаешь чтобы вот эти вопрос
where again Zaporozhye region,
снять где ещё раз Запорожская область
even if you held some kind of referendum
даже если вы провели какой-то референдум
under occupation, Zaporozhye itself held
под оккупацией само Запорожье проводило
a referendum,
референдум
listen Well, who held it? Well, part of the
слушайте Ну а кто проводил Ну часть
Zaporozhye region not including the city of
Запорожской области не включая город
Zaporozhye held a referendum, yes, that is, I’m
Запорожье провело рефере да то есть я
correct  I understand that if Khimki holds a
правильно понимаю если Химки проведут
referendum, then we can sort of assume that
референдум да то можно типа считать что
Moscow held a referendum
Москва провела референдум
Yes, I understand that you have this, well, I kind of
Да я понимаю что у вам это ну как бы
agree that a lot of things don’t seem to
много согласен что многое как бы там не
fit into your understanding, okay,
вписывается в понимание ваши ладно
look, wait, wait, one small
смотри Подожди подожди один маленький
little moment, look, look, a very, very
маленький момент смотри смотри очень
important point  a very important point
очень важный момент очень важный момент
Listen Listen Listen please I’ll
Послушай Послушай Послушай пожалуйста
say a very important point and just Oh, you’re
очень важный момент скажу и просто О ты
already tired of it, let’s
уже задолбал давай всё в следующий раз
talk about another topic next time Yes Listen,
поговорим на другую тему ещё Да Слушай
you’re just so sla Let’s give
ну ты просто ну сла
you a plus sign, he deserved it,
Дава поставь ты плюсик ему сподобалось
dokin cheney
докин чени
you, write to my Telegram directly at the same time
тибе Пиши на мий Telegram прямо зараз
VN and
ось ВН а
pok more and more
пок це дуже и дуже
respectfully
важливо